

# RELEVANT PAGES jangebert.com LinkedIn GitHub

## **LANGUAGES**

## **GERMAN**Native

## SPANISH Native

## ENGLISH Qualification IELTS Overall: 7.5

Speaking: 7.0 Listening: 8.0 Reading: 8.5 Writing: 7.0

## **NORWEGIAN** Qualification VOX Niveau B1

## **Jan Gebert**

Email: jangebert@jangebert.com

Age: 30 years old | Nationality: German/Argentinian

Data Scientist and Petroleum Engineer with strong background in data modelling and expertise building scalable solutions and with data visualisation tools. Experience as Data Engineering Technical Lead in Merkur Innovation Lab, building the Data Warehouse and Predictive Models. Previously working in E-commerce SaaS as Data Scientist, working closely with Product Team. Two years of experience working as a Reservoir Engineer in the Oil and Gas industry. Supporting clients in their Simulation workflow and delivering training courses on Reservoir Engineering to clients.

## **WORKING EXPERIENCE**



## DATA SCIENTIST/ENGINEER- Merkur Innovation Lab

Graz, Austria (February 2021 - August 2023)

Main responsibilities: Design and implementation of data pipelines ETLs with different Databases (PostgreSQL/Oracle/MSSQL/Adabas). Development of data modeling processes to create algorithms and predictive models as a basis for carrying out various analyses. Design, implement and manage an organization's data architecture. Onboarding and mentoring of new data engineering team members.

## 2020

#### **DATA SCIENTIST** - Tiendanube S.A.

Buenos Aires, Argentina (February 2020 - January 2021)

**Main responsibilities:** Created dashboards for C-Level Management. Automatization of daily reports with python. Design and Automation of A/B testing. Bug prioritization using GitHub API and reporting with Google Sheets and Slack. Page load speed monitoring. Data Manipulation and table creation in PostgreSQL. Implemented a tool to identify failed pipelines across Data Team.

## 2018

#### **RESERVOIR ENGINEER** - SLB

Buenos Aires, Argentina (September 2018 - January 2020)

**Main responsibilities:** Instructor for Simulation Software courses and workshops. Python and Visual Basic scripting for data cleaning and preparation for simulations. Building strong customer relationships with external clients through client visits, support and workshops.

## **EDUCATION**

2020-2022

## Msc. Data and Information Science

FH Joanneum Graz -Austria

2019-2019

## **Diploma in Applied Data Science**

Universidad Austral

Capital Federal - Buenos Aires - Argentina

2012-2018

## **Petroleum Engineering**

Instituto Tecnológico de Buenos Aires (ITBA) Capital Federal - Buenos Aires - Argentina

## **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

Python/R C#/Javascript PowerBI/Tableau

SQL AWS Azure